- Previously on Tracker...
- I know you think
- I pushed Dad off that cliff.
- I saw you there.
There was somebody else
in those woods that night.
Mom. if there's something
that you know about Dad...
Colter. for everyone's sake.
leave it be.
The man you saw
on the cliff the night
Dad died... his name's Otto.
Mom's the one
that sent him up there.
Did you throw my dad
off that cliff?
I did.
- Why?
- 'Cause your mother
asked for my help.
What's so damn important
you came all the way up here
- to talk about?
- My father. Ashton Shaw.
Lot of those
academic types up here.
They hightailed it
after the accident.
Hey. Russell.
it's your favorite brother.
I found out who Dad was
working with before he died.
Serena Jukic.
Call me back.
Wally?
Wally!
Help.
Somebody help!
All right.
Hey. I got you.
Just don't move. okay?
Hold still.
What do we got?
- I can't move my arm.
- Can't move your arm?
Okay. let me take a look.
How's that?
Yeah. that's broken.
All right. look at me.
Hey. hey. look at me.
What about anything else?
Anything else around your body?
I don't know. just my arm.
Just your arm. Okay.
All right.
I'm gonna stabilize the...
the arm
before I get you out
of here. okay?
Not gonna lie to you.
it's not gonna feel good.
but it's necessary.
Don't want that fracture
to shift.
Put this on you.
Here we go. We're gonna go on...
on three. Ready?
One. two. three. Here we go.
You all right? You all right?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Slow. deep breaths. okay?
You control your breathing.
Focus on that. you let me
do the rest. okay?
- How long you been riding?
- Five years.
Five years. All right.
Well. it doesn't look like
your bike's gonna make it
out of here.
but the good news is...
you are. all right?
We'll do it together. Here.
Some water.
- There you go.
- Mm.
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna hike
back up that hill.
All right.
You're gonna make it
to your feet here. okay?
Use your legs and your good arm.
- Ready?
- Re...
Nice.
There we go. There we go.
Catch your breath.
- You good?
- Mm-hmm.
- We got this. right?
Okay. Here we go.
Put your arm around me.
- We're off.
- Okay.
Looks like we made it.
Thanks.
I don't know
what I would've done.
You're welcome.
Wally.
- Thank you.
- He's gonna be okay.
His. uh. arm is broken.
Hey.
There he is. My hero.
What in the world
are you doing here? Come here.
I got the meats. Yeah?
Look at this... some lamb kebabs
with my special rub.
I figure you could whip up
some sides.
Yeah. yeah. You don't call?
- You don't write? Nothing?
- What's the fun in that?
I did track you down
pretty easy. though.
Well. yeah. Reenie.
Gentleman never reveals
his sources.
- Hmm.
- Okay. If you got some brews...
- Yep.
- We can get busy on these kebabs.
I got a little. uh. Cambodian
black Kampot peppercorn action.
so you're gonna want some beers.
Great.
Oh. yeah.
Let's have it.
- For you.
- Thank you.
Now...
What are you really doing here?
What. I can't just drop in
on my brother and...
You found Dr. Jukic. right?
The details line up.
She. uh... she changed her name.
went offline.
probably for good reason.
She was working with Dad on that
Chrono Stasis project in Alaska.
I did get some intel
on what they were
trying to do.
but most of it was redacted.
Yeah. it's
pretty out-there stuff.
- So. where is she?
- Not too far from here.
Huh.
- I need to talk to her.
- Okay. I'll go with you.
But we need to make
a pit stop first: Echo Ridge.
Might be the last time
we see the house.
Maybe pick up a few things.
What do you mean?
Mom's selling the place.
I didn't know that.
That's 'cause
you two don't talk.
You're right.
Yeah. I need to talk to her.
hear her side.
It'd be good to clear the air.
you know? We did.
- And look at us now.
- That's right.
All right. It smells great. man.
Oh. you're gonna love this.
You're not coming?
Nah. it's better
if it's just you two.
I'm gonna give one last look
around the place.
Hey. Colter...
give her a chance. would you?
Yeah.
Colter.
Mom.
Come on. Sit.
Let me put on a pot of coffee.
Hey.
Been a while.
Well. you still got us
all out here
trying to figure you out.
you son of a bitch.
Yeah. but maybe that's
what you wanted.
I don't know.
Keep telling myself
it don't matter.
And maybe we're living
in some kind of simulation.
But...
But here we are.
No matter where we go. we keep
coming back to this place.
Like an echo.
Is that why they call it
Echo Ridge?
You probably knew that.
though. didn't you?
Yeah. thank you.
I. uh...
I know you blame me for
what happened to your father.
Russell told me
you went to see Otto.
That's right. I did.
I'm sorry that I lied to you.
I'm sorry for all that hurt
that it has caused.
but everything I did
was to protect you
and Russell and Dory.
What can you tell me
about Dad's time in Alaska?
Alaska.
I know that
the research he was doing
- was funded by the government.
- It was.
And maybe...
maybe he was doing work
he shouldn't have been doing.
That last summer.
when he came back
from his time up there.
he-he was changed.
Yeah.
Yeah. I think
we all remember that.
Yeah. he was shut down
and broken inside.
He'd stopped sleeping.
He. uh... he said the government
was out to get him.
- You ever ask him why?
- He didn't let me
into that part of his life.
and if I asked
too many questions. he'd just...
um...
he'd get angry.
You know. I want you
to understand something.
I tried protecting all of you.
But he was spiraling.
He had lost his grip on reality.
I just had to get you kids
out of here.
Did he hurt you?
He. um...
He didn't allow us
to leave. and...
I had to do something.
You called Otto.
I didn't know what else
to do. but...
I did not tell him
to kill your father.
And that's the truth.
I believe you.
You know. for a long time.
you let me believe
that Russell was...
responsible for Dad's death.
Why did you...
There were forces
against your father.
and I was scared
that they would come after you
and Russell
if you started looking into
the circumstances of his death.
I was your mother.
first and foremost.
I just wanted my kids
to be safe.
God. this place. huh?
Well. I'm glad
you're selling it.
You deserve a fresh start. Mom.
Wow.
Yeah.
Remember this hunk of junk?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. Look at this.
Dad said. uh. I could have this
once I got my license.
You didn't want something
that actually worked?
It worked once. didn't it?
Remember. we took it
to the lake. went fishing?
It was a great day.
One of the last great days
with him. actually.
Well. didn't it break down
on the way home?
You know. it did. didn't it?
Yeah.
Look at this. Remember how crazy
he was about his tools?
Oh. yeah. Lot of rules.
How'd it go with Mom?
Good. I think good.
Thank you.
- I'll take that.
- All right.
We had a deal... Dr. Jukic.
What do you know that I don't?
Got an address.
Northern Nevada.
Pretty remote.
What do you suppose
she's doing out there?
Hiding out. considering
what it took to find her.
Well. maybe it has something
to do with the work
she was doing with Dad
in Alaska.
- Yeah. could be. Worth a shot.
- Yeah.
You sure you want to come with?
Yeah. I got nothing
better to do.
Well. you could
stick around here.
fix up this hunk of junk.
Ha. Pass.
Nah. what's dead is dead.
Yeah. so...
thinking it's probably best if
you let me do all the talking.
Why? 'Cause you're
so good with words?
- And women?
- Well...
- Can I at least knock?
- Be my guest.
Hi. We're looking
for Serena Jukic.
We were told she lives here.
You got the wrong place.
You missed the sign.
This place is protected
by Smith & Wesson.
Well. you want to see what
Sig Sauer has to say about that?
Whoa. whoa.
Before we get into all that.
look. we-we don't want
any trouble.
We're looking for Dr. Jukic.
We were told she lived here.
She used to work
with our father years back.
We're just looking
for information is all.
I already told you.
I don't know her.
Now. get off the property.
It's all right. Paul.
You're Ashton's boys.
You're Dr. Jukic?
Nobody's called me that
in years. but yes...
I am.
Come in.
Thank you.
Your safety was on.
and your fly was down.
You were working
at the Chrono Stasis Institute
with our father.
and David Pearson.
a behavioral biologist.
and Walt Fleming.
a neurologist. right?
Those two gentlemen.
they died shortly after
leaving the institute.
You've done your research.
What were you working on?
We know it was dark stuff.
We just want to know what.
It's not something
I'm prepared to talk about.
Well. you didn't have
to let us in. but you did.
Must be something
you want to say.
Look. w-we're just trying
to fill in the gaps.
figure out what happened
to our father
that summer in Alaska.
Your father was a difficult man.
Too smart for his own good
and stubborn as hell.
and one of the best mentors
I ever had.
Truth is. if I'd listened
to him back then.
maybe I'd be able
to live with myself now.
What were you researching?
Genetic predisposition as it
relates to savant syndrome.
In particular. Ashton's work
on the preponderance
of the seven-hertz anomalies
in the prefrontal cortex
and their correlation
with elevated abilities.
So you were taking geniuses
and you were
stretching the limits
- of their capabilities.
- Precisely.
But the university
where he was teaching
refused funding for his work.
They denied him tenure.
He told me that.
But DARPA wasn't afraid
of his research.
Neural augmentation.
astral projection.
remote viewing...
we were looking into all of it.
DARPA.
So they weaponized
your research. didn't they?
Yes.
Yeah. should've known
it was psionics.
Psionics?
You know. psychics.
paranormal abilities.
Folks at the Pentagon wanting
to keep up with what Russia
was doing on that front.
And our father believed
in all that?
This wasn't theoretical.
We saw it with our own eyes.
Our. uh... our mother said
something happened that summer.
that he...
snapped.
Ashton was uneasy with
the real-world application.
And...
then they brought in
a new batch of test subjects...
With a high degree
of brain plasticity.
You were testing children.
And our... our father
was okay with that.
- just. uh. testing children?
- No.
He thought a line
had been crossed. but...
we went along with it. and...
- then there was an accident.
- What happened?
A child died in Alaska.
We... She wasn't on my team.
We were told that it was
due to a heart defect
unrelated to our testing. but...
your father just lost it.
He tried to have
the program shut down.
So they doxed
him. tried to discredit him.
- They did.
- And what about you?
You continued with the program?
He warned me.
but I was young and ambitious.
and I didn't listen.
And back then. I truly believed
that that child's death
was an accident.
So they shut the program down
in Alaska.
and then what.
they just move it?
Yes. and I followed.
And eventually. they turned
against me when I tried to
protect
one of the test subjects.
This kid named Danny Kellerman.
He was extraordinarily gifted.
He was eight years old
when I first met him.
I was told he was an orphan.
You know how that works. Danny?
Just off-the-charts IQ.
and he had...
other unique abilities.
I didn't mean to. but I became
very attached to him.
and I tried to protect him.
We were doing
a remote viewing session.
What do you see. Danny?
I'm in my old house.
A-And I see my mom...
in the kitchen.
He told me his mom
was still alive.
I thought he was making it up.
but...
I went to his old house.
and I saw his mother.
I looked into his background.
He matched a boy who died in
a car accident with his father.
I learned that the program
had staged the accident
and killed his father.
They even showed his mother
the bodies.
You confront 'em?
They took Danny away.
I never saw him again.
I tried to look for him.
but they revoked
my security clearance
and started threatening me.
The same thing they did
to our father.
Yes.
I heard rumors that
they'd expanded the program
beyond the original six
test subjects.
that they found success
in pairing them up to expand
their mental abilities.
What were they using them for?
They were forcing them
to use their skills
in real-life situations.
DoD applications.
How did you get out?
Wasn't easy.
And then a month
after I left. I...
heard that his mom had died
of a mysterious drug overdose.
You think that's the program?
I know it was.
I never had children of my own.
but Danny was a son to me.
Been seven years.
and I worry about him
every single day.
But I know what would happen
if I go look for him.
Then we'll try to find him.
Well. I'd love to know
how you think you're gonna
find this kid...
who's an adult now. by the way.
if he's still alive.
Having second thoughts
about going along?
Well. I think I've heard
enough to know
a little hesitancy is warranted.
you know?
It's not like we can walk in
to one of these places
and just take him.
Russell. you heard
what she said. right?
This-this guy is like a...
he's like a prisoner.
He didn't want this
with his life.
They took him. They took a kid.
We got to at least look for him.
It's what Dad would want.
I guess I can't let you
go get your head blown off.
Thank you.
although I've managed so far.
Mm. Barely.
Yeah.
So. they seem pretty sure
they're being watched.
Let's see what Paul has to say.
Sorry about before.
with the gun.
It's understood.
So. how long
have you known Dr. Jukic?
We've been together
a couple years.
I know about everything
she's been through.
It's why we've been
on edge lately.
Okay.
Did something happen recently?
Got a van on my security cams.
Started driving by a few
weeks ago... no license plate.
That's Uncle Sam keeping tabs.
letting you know they know.
Which means they're gonna know
that we were here.
Do you have someplace safe
you can go?
- I can find one.
- Well. I'd go there now.
There's gonna be blowback.
Take this.
If you hear anything
about Danny...
You'll be the first to know.
I promise.
Thank you.
Yep. All right. be safe.
Randy. hey.
did you get my message?
Yeah. sure did.
Hey. buddy.
Good to hear your voice.
Russ. man.
Good to hear from you. too.
Okay. so I looked
into Danny Kellerman.
and Dr. Jukic's story
checks out.
This article here says
that he and his father
were killed in a car crash.
And you're saying
that it was staged?
I think so.
so they could take Danny.
Okay. Well. he'd be
about 23 years old right now.
I ran his photo
through this aging app
just to see
what he'd look like today.
Sent you the photo.
Other than that.
the trail goes pretty cold.
Yeah. what about the security
footage of the surveillance van?
No windows. no plates.
I'd say it's government.
I hope you double-gloved
on this. digitally speaking.
Yeah. don't want to get
rawdogged by Uncle Sam.
So. what do you think
they were doing there?
I mean. best guess...
simple surveillance.
You know. let me try something.
Okay.
Interesting.
Her Wi-Fi signal slows down
whenever the van's near.
The van would have its own
Wi-Fi network. wouldn't it?
Yeah. it's probably
sucking up bandwidth
from Dr. Jukic's channel.
Yeppers.
Got an IP routing address.
and it's connected
to a Ford E-Transit van.
I'm tracking where that is now.
And I found it.
Just sent you a pin.
All right. got it.
Thanks. Randy. Appreciate you.
I'm gonna try to meet up
with an old buddy of mine.
ask him about this little
government project.
Not something I can bring
a. uh. plus-one to.
so I'll need you to stand by.
- I'll give you a ride.
- Great.
Got a tingle on file 6AB.
Two phones just popped up
in her radius.
Oh. that's interesting.
One of them is ours.
Russell Shaw.
Okay. We need to escalate this.
Just keep driving.
- Who are you?
- Don't worry about that.
Who's your boss?
Lot of people.
Who had you watching Dr. Jukic?
I-I don't know
what you're talking about.
That's good.
Now. pull over right here.
Wait. wait. Uh. Jukic.
Right. that's. uh...
Let me think.
You try that again.
I'll pull the trigger.
You understand me?
Put this thing in park.
Good.
Now who's your boss?
I don't know.
Just get a list
of people to watch.
We get our money on time.
we don't ask any questions.
See. I think you do know.
You're gonna give me a name.
Shaw.
Felton.
Thanks for meeting me.
Thought you were out.
I am.
Kinda.
You know how these things go.
Yeah. I do.
The only reason I'm here is
'cause of what you did
for me in Panama City.
Ah. I was just doing my job.
It was more than that.
Yes. it was.
But that's not
why I reached out.
Guessing it's not to talk
about your feelings.
You know I'm dead inside.
Me. too.
Just so we're clear.
after this. we're square. yeah?
It's that bad. huh?
Guys have gotten their names
on the "quiet forever" list
for a lot less.
Okay. so this Chrono Stasis
program
is still active?
Come on. Shaw.
When have you ever seen
a covert DoD program go offline?
Mm. Good point.
Of course. it's mutated.
Deep black. USAP.
Unacknowledged?
You feeling my caution now?
If they learn that
you are poking around.
they will wipe the slate clean
and burn anybody else
who has touched it
to the ground.
present company not excluded.
I didn't think you were the type
to get the yips
and fill up your boots.
I'm old.
I've got people who care for me.
A cat. even.
No need to overshare.
My advice:
stop asking questions.
Trying to save a kid who's in
the program. a Danny Kellerman.
They snatched him 15 years ago.
- You know the name.
- Yeah.
I heard he provided key intel
for Operation Red Claw in Syria.
Is he still alive?
Can't confirm that.
But even if he were.
you know how that goes.
Yeah. Popped. pilled.
and then tossed.
If they're lucky.
Most are decommed quietly
and forever.
Good luck to me. then.
You're gonna need
more than that.
Copy that.
Keep my name out of this.
Lose my number
and have a good life.
Hey. Felton.
We'll always have Panama City.
- Randy. what do you got?
- Yo.
I got Reenie here. too.
Had to pull out the big guns.
Hey. this is a hell of a mess
you and Russell
- found yourselves in again.
- So. the company paying
for surveillance is a shell.
I won't bore you with the how.
but just know they're owned
by Dorix Logistics.
Hmm. They connected to the DoD?
Well. indirectly.
They're a private military
contract company.
Their work is classified.
but I did find
that their main focus
is advanced weaponry.
They were having
Dr. Jukic watched.
so maybe they're running
the whole thing.
I mean. that would make sense.
Which means maybe they know
what happened to Danny.
Where are they located?
HQ is in Virginia.
but they got buildings all over.
Okay. got it.
Will you keep digging?
I'm about ready
to pick up Russell.
Maybe he's got some information.
we can narrow this down.
Okay.
How'd we do?
Well. it's as we suspected.
This Chrono Stasis program
is still active.
but it's a USAP now.
What's that?
Unacknowledged
Special Access Program.
Basically means that the. uh...
the name. the purpose.
the funding is all unknown.
There's really only
one reason to do that.
That's to take
a theoretical research program
and make it practical.
So Dr. Jukic was correct.
They're using these kids
for combat.
Oh. yeah.
Remote target acquisitions.
magnetic field alterations.
It's crazy stuff.
- You trust this guy?
- No.
I mean. I don't trust anybody.
But as far as contacts go.
I'd say he's 98% reliable.
Does he know
if Danny's still alive?
No. but...
But what?
They treat these kids
like assets.
not like human beings.
They do whatever it takes
to get results.
So they pump 'em full of drugs.
uh. electroshock therapy.
uh. meditative induction.
You think he's dead?
I'm saying I think
if he's alive.
he's probably broken
or fubar as all get-out.
Yeah.
Lola. draw what you see.
I don't see anything.
Remember what I said
about lying. hmm?
I know you see it.
I can't. I don't want to.
Lola. let's not be difficult.
Do you remember
what happened last time?
- Get her out!
- Danny! No. Danny. please!
No! Danny. please!
- Stop. Stop. Let her go!
- No. please. please!
Danny!
Danny. sit down.
No!
Sit!
Now. then.
Let's you and I get started.
Starting to wonder
if Dad ever used us
for any of his experiments.
I mean. not... not this stuff.
but remember those little tests
he used to do?
Mm. Oh. yeah. Yeah. yeah.
The "getting over our own fears"
kind of thing?
The. uh... studying the Stoics.
- Ugh.
- Your favorite.
Epictetus? Remember that guy?
I mean. you were always good
at that stuff. Me. not so much.
What do you suppose he's doing
researching psionics anyway?
I mean. all this
astral projection
and. uh. uh.
precognition stuff. uh...
Brother. you got no idea.
I've seen remote viewing.
I can't explain it.
but it worked.
- You've seen it firsthand?
- I have.
Yeah. when I was back in Yemen.
There was a rumor
that the Houthis had
some big weapons cache
hidden somewhere.
so it was our mission
to go find it. right?
Someone from Army high command
brings in this guy.
He was a little weird.
You know. "dead behind the eyes"
kind of a thing.
They put a map in front of him.
He sits down.
he closes his eyes.
kind of goes someplace.
Then. boom...
pops open.
points to some random spot
in the-the Hejaz Mountains.
and they tell us to go.
Now. obviously.
we're thinking this is
some sort of fishing expedition.
it's a waste of our time.
We get to the coordinates.
and I kid you not.
there is a cave the size
of a warehouse that is filled...
filled with all kinds of stuff.
How do you explain that?
Some people are really good at
pattern recognition. you know?
I would say maybe he's familiar
with the geography. right?
He knew what he was looking for:
something remote.
something large.
something that spot heat imaging
won't penetrate.
We had all that information.
No. this was
something different.
It was...
it was freaky. you know?
Besides. it doesn't matter
if you believe in it.
Apparently. somebody does.
They're keeping a secret
government program running.
Well. that's true.
And they care enough to kill
to keep it secret.
Apparently.
So. what's the next move?
Well. I got Reenie and Randy
chasing down this company
I think might be connected:
Dorix Logistics.
- Dor... D-O-R-I-X?
- Mm-hmm.
I know that name.
Yeah.
it's a military contractor.
I think maybe they're running
the whole thing.
I mean. it makes sense.
It's a classic move.
You know. you take it offshore.
you bury it.
The government keeps
their hands clean
by subbing it out
to a private company.
which is really just a front.
I'm thinking maybe
they still have Danny.
I've got Randy digging
deeper into it.
Yeah. be my guest. just. uh.
take whatever you want.
Make a quick call.
What's up.
Colter? I ain't got nothing yet.
No. man. it's-it's Russell.
the-the smarter.
better-looking brother.
Uh. I think I've got
something for you on Dorix.
That's good.
'cause I don't exactly know
what I'm looking for.
Try pharmaceutical orders
related to
neurological disorders.
Okay.
All right. I got a large order
for sedatives
and antipsychotics.
Yeah. I mean.
they're probably using those
to control the subjects.
Is-is that a repeat order.
Randy.
going to the same location?
Let's see.
Bingo.
Couple times a year
for the last five years
to an address outside
of Twin Falls. Idaho.
And I just sent it to you.
And I'm betting that's where
they're keeping the subjects.
- Worth a shot.
- Yeah. Nice work.
You checked in late.
Five minutes.
- Shaw made contact?
- He did.
He and his brother know more
than they should.
Did you tell him what would
happen if he didn't stop?
Shaw doesn't exactly
grok that concept.
but yeah. I laid it out.
What about his brother Colter?
Goes double for him.
Well...
that's unfortunate. So...
now I have two problems.
I told you. I have this handled.
Do you?
Russell Shaw put you in.
You need to find a way out.
That's a lot of security.
They're guarding something.
All right. so we wait
for them to leave.
we matriculate in there.
find Danny...
Bob's your uncle.
I don't think "matriculate"
means what you think it means.
Hmm?
It's Reenie.
Reenie. hey.
Did you get any information...
Hey. Reenie. How you been?
- You need to do this right now?
- What. we can't
exchange pleasantries
like normal people?
- Hi. Russell.
- Reenie. did you get
any information on Dorix?
Well. it looks like
they bought out the entire town
with some investments and
well-placed donations to civic
and law enforcement groups.
That's textbook.
And a journalist who was
investigating Dorix
went missing last May.
No police investigation.
FBI had a look.
but quickly shut it down.
Looks like we're on our own.
Looks like it. Keep me posted.
Yeah. will do. Thanks. Reenie.
You want to do this?
Here we go.
Yeah.
I've been trying to reach you.
Just finishing
something up here.
We've got another one for you.
It's two brothers:
Colter and Russell Shaw.
Send me the details.
That's far enough.
Drop the gun.
Or what?
Or I put one through your skull.
Last chance before the bullets
start flying. friend.
Don't do anything stupid.
Me?
Never.
Hi. Danny.
Who are you?
My name's Colter Shaw.
Dr. Jukic sent me to find you.
Dr. Jukic?
She told me what
they're doing to you.
Come with me.
Let's get you out of here.
I'm not going anywhere.
I press this button.
and this room gets flooded
by a dozen armed guards.
Okay.
Well. how about we don't push
the button. Danny?
I understand you're scared.
Look at me. You can trust me.
I will keep you safe.
You don't understand.
I can't leave.